{
    "id": "6353c8af6c5c486d90b780beb84eaf24",
    "title": "Simple Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. him yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "was seeing",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. his letter yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "received",
                "have received",
                "was receiving"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………….. school last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will leave",
                "was leaving",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Last night I …………………………….. sleep well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "didn't",
                "hadn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………………. asleep while he was driving.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fell",
                "was falling",
                "had fallen"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… a new bicycle last week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "have bought",
                "had bought"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………….. our breakfast half an hour ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "finished",
                "have finished",
                "had finished"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I was in the US, I …………………………….. Chicago, Boston and California.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visiting",
                "visited",
                "was visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………….. an old classmate of mine at the library.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was seeing",
                "saw",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………… that she would not go.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "says",
                "said",
                "was saying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}